I just want to share something real quick something real quick
Let's see
This is our last night on
On Alexandra's channel she shared a little bit of a Zay as recent interview. I just want to show you
Part of it, okay
Thank you, Alex. I'm covering some more truths.
Okay. It's an interesting part. Hope you guys find it interesting.
Let's be a short stream. What's up? Hey, what's up? How are you? Hey, here you go. Do you see it on the screen yet? Let me see. There we go.
But yet you're going around calling people pedophiles
You know, if it wasn't so expensive if it wasn't a thought process that I can't get paid or I would lose money
I would sue the fuck out of you
You know, and that's what really needs to happen. You know, youtube needs to get rid of a bunch of you people
Okay, you serve no purpose. You just get on here and you spread fake lies because your ass is hurt
Okay, Kate over there talking about groomers baby girl. You don't forget the thousands of dollars you put in my pocket
You're calling you. Oh, so she donated a whole bunch to him, too
Really groomer, but you forgot about the thousands of dollars that you put in my pocket
forget about the thousands of dollars that not only you put in my pocket but you siphoned to
Barry and Barry put it in my pocket. Really? I didn't know any of that until just now. Really?
Oh, look at that. Someone coming in with the information for Psyche. Okay.
Yeah. So, so what did it call me again? A predator protector.
Hmm.
And I lost my support. I lost all my support. I don't think so.
Well, so I got for you. Why is my screen like this?
Long
Oh here. Oh the heck
I don't know. I don't know
Interesting Kate
Interesting and you denied it. What did you say on your page? Let me see
It's what you say to me about that. Let me see
You said
Sacky cries about low. Oh, there's allied master computer. Oh, you're posting Tony stuff. Okay, funny. Okay fine. Maybe I can strike that okay
Where did the clip go? I got it some more. Let me see I see
Oh my gosh, life's e-bagging, providing safe space for predators.
Cult of Psyche. See my previous post. I didn't donate thousands. That's a bold-faced lie,
and no proof has been shown of such claims. Running with lies is a bad look,
but you know what has been shown to be true? Brandon is indeed, okay, yeah, sure, okay,
and you are standing firm with him and losing all your support. Okay, 11 people.
Wow, okay, well, all my support.
Yeah, got him
Got him, let's play the clip again. That was an interesting clip, you know
IRL news time. Oh, actually Alexander did a great a great live last. It was actually this morning
And we can play it again she did was a great great live last night, so
Okay, let me just go back to this
Three minutes 19. Here we go. I'll do it. I'll play a little bit more. Here we go. I
Don't think I'm losing all my support but
Let's go
Yeah, attraction psyche it's a very strange energy between them I am going to do a stream exploring
The energy you know, it's like it you should do
like you know how some
tarot card readers do readings
about celebrities or
about current events you should do a reading in regards to
crystal and gamble and
See what pops up
That would be interesting to watch
I wonder what their birthdays are.
I don't even know what their birthdays are.
Like, I wonder if they're compatible or opposing signs.
Hey, Jamie.
Or what?
But yet you're going around calling people pedophiles.
You know, if it wasn't so expensive, if it wasn't a thought process that I can't get paid or I would lose money, I would sue the fuck out of you.
You know, and that's what really needs to happen. You know, YouTube needs to get rid of a bunch of you people
Okay, you serve no purpose. You just get on here and you spread fake lies because your ass is hurt
Okay, Kate over there talking about groomers. Baby girls, you don't forget the thousands of dollars you put in my pocket
You're calling you. Oh, so she donated a whole bunch to him, too
Really?
Groomer, but you forgot about the thousands of dollars that you put in my pocket
You
Forget about the thousands of dollars that not only you put in my pocket, but you siphon to Barry and Barry put it in my pocket
Really?
Hey, Katie, how are you? I
Don't know I
Don't know
They please do show those receipts
You know
Please do because this woman
Kate
Posting Allied master computer what low viewership I got 26 people in seven minutes 40 seconds
It's not too bad. I had 60 people last night
Not low viewership. It's a
Know isn't that crazy? Isn't that crazy Jason J. Delmonico? Isn't that crazy?
Bet nobody does that really oh, please oh sure
Yeah, I'm like live on air during tarot cards, and that's chat CPT. Okay, you're out
Please
I've done over, I've done over like almost 2000 readings on Etsy and Dear 2022. That was way before chat GPT, wasn't it?
But anyway, fake news
Jason Delmonico
Readings are live. They're not typed. You're just
Hater, I'm pretty good this morning. I'm good. I'm pretty good this morning. I
You know
Enough for a little bit. Let's see. I'm just waiting on something
Then I'll get my day started
Well tricks has been found I believe but you know, that's not your business right there
Not a minute, and I'm not you know
Animals, like, what are you talking about?
I mean, it's like, well, okay, just attack me,
attack my credibility,
because you don't like what's being said,
but the truth, right?
Go ahead.
Have I got to meet you?
Greet you?
Hi, I said hello, Jamie.
Oh, last night, I'm sorry, I fell asleep.
I'm sorry, I fell asleep.
Do we have a meeting?
I'm sorry.
My plan to you. Oh, well, hold on. Looks like your plan to say anything has been all has been a I'm sorry. Oh
I didn't even see your comment
Well last night. I fell asleep. I'm sorry. I
Was very tired if you'd like to meet today. We happy to
We did a we did a power last night
Um, so anyway, we will, we will, we will today if you want to. Okay? Good. Okay. Yeah. I mean, it's like, oh yeah, there's gonna be, um, you know, it's just basically Tony, it's just basically Tony, maybe some of Kate's goons, uh, going after me in the chat, so just ignore them, you know, most of them are, are hidden, but um, you know, mods, mods, you see what they're saying, I know you can help me take care of that.
What should we look at? I like to pack yourself up channel though. I do like that channel a lot. Let me see if I got
Something we can watch today on that that'd be good
Okay, so let me have a look. I think I have oh here we go
You have the channel
Yesterday we watched a great one
Today we're today we're gonna watch about
Crystal and Sandman versus INX and I think INX is gonna walk away the W. I'm
just predicting. I'm just predicting here okay. I'm not bad. Let me see. Here we go.
There's that. Okay and let's have a look at this clip.
Pack yourself up channel pack yourself up has actually been an interesting channel. Like it's actually
Been in pretty impressive and I do recommend it's PCK YAS ELF UP I believe, okay
And I think it's time for some of these PDF obsessed
You know, especially
I don't know, you know, I guess she might need to.
Okay, let me see, one second.
Let's watch.
And I like INX.
See that's some good info.
Okay, let me see.
Crystal and Sam and versus I and X
Okay, ready what's up, what's up everybody here we go let's watch this
Got the broom. That's what that's what salmon really looks like. Okay. There we go
back crystal so that you're playing games and I'm going to show all our
communication crystal show your call on crystal you were blowing me up you talk
shit about bride you know you're the one doing shit I left alone you can you
Come at me when Q was talking to you.
You said he's gonna dodge me, you fat bitch.
Yo shut up you fat bitch, you're the one that's fat.
You're your pet, I have your real picture.
You're fat, I have it, I'm not fat.
Crystal even knows it, she's seeing me
because she's a real picture.
I'm not 180.
I'm at 122.
I was it, I was it.
I saw her picture, she looks good.
I was heavy in 2016, everybody's seeing my picture.
She's 122, you wanna swat, you wanna what,
you gonna swat me?
Who said anything? That's what I didn't say anybody
No, you see you were trying in the dark
Crystal I'm asking you
Yeah, you wanted to talk to me and
You
Speak I'm talking to crystal what she did
I don't know what I have the truth about
What I was wanting to talk I don't talk to you just stop
Dr. She's the one that tries to get in touch with me, and I show that.
Bitch, don't go fuck another kid, you're the one that's into Q and Q said you wanted to
screw him.
Okay?
Are you not watching?
How you had to hide from him?
Stop mentioning me, I'm going to start recording other lives because he's the most it.
I don't want to do anything.
I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to me, I'm going to show it to
anymore, okay? You should have never reached out to me when I was the last one. Why are you here then?
Why are you here now? I'm just asking you to leave me alone. That's not good. Leave you though.
All right, well then she keeps on talking. You're asking me when I hit man, you fucking
person. That was in 2020 when I was there, but that way you did a lot. Look at the communication
Me okay
Yeah, people like you need to go to jail.
Oh, you're a bitch.
Look, you were great.
You were great.
I'm going to answer.
Look at your picture with the black guy and an air mattress behind you.
Why are you making fun of him?
Tell yourself.
You don't like being, your looks being made up.
And I'm not going to you.
You're fine.
You don't like your looks shown, though, either, Crystal.
That's why they asked you to show face.
I've already showed myself on camera earlier.
Thank you very much.
Well, I don't care.
I do face time.
And you had none of them.
You ugly fuck.
me again I just don't want any communication with your crystal you
My mother was
should never reach out and look at my I have some actually footage of a crystal
with a use those videos I have some footage of crystal and uh
Because I have a group that you've seen Chelsea that blend you.
I don't give a fuck! Stop bringing me up. Stop throwing up my real life. I don't care.
That's why I'm here. Stop bringing it up.
You want me to drag your family?
Well, I'll figure that out.
and that she showed you, okay?
I showed the rest of it.
What she showed me?
Oh, no, go ahead and show, go look at it.
I put the microphone next to her,
you weren't hitting on him.
And you were doing it for me.
Leave Ella alone.
She said to me,
she was talking shit about Ella yesterday.
I like Ella, and she knows everything.
She's shit about her.
I like everything.
I couldn't feel, I didn't see everything
because I haven't been recording you.
I never tried to.
And I told her everything.
I told her everything I said to you.
You were talking shit about her,
and I'm gonna, she's gonna.
Sorry, that was old. Hold on one second. Okay, let me let me have a look one second
You're the only really the only sloppy person in Sam and this is only slop
Okay, what do you have a recommendation? Okay, let me see one second
Let me just get to my channel
Okay
You can link it if you want okay
That was old. Okay, let me
Let's see what we got
Give a recommendation
There's I see betas group
You see
Just let me know what you want. I should play play. I
should play
I see this I see this crystal and stuff
Let me see crystal and news while we played today Chris this old the clover crystal and talking about
Vita and stuff, but let me see this
I'll play this I'll play this clip over there. This is from grateful. Okay, if you go ahead and blink your channel
This is Chelsea regarding CrystalAnne's bogus charge, okay?
I'm sorry, this is a little bit off. Okay, there we go, I can get...
There we go. I don't know why I'm looking like that. I'll just take myself off the screen,
but here, I'll share the screen. Okay, share, okay, and let me just take this off.
Okay
Okay, this is Chelsea. This is Vianna's wife, and she's the one I was talking about in the last video.
She didn't even know Crystal Anne, and Crystal had that false case against Chelsea's now husband, Vianna.
So this is her talking about Crystal.
So I have never actually been alive before. This is a new thing, but
Today has been a day, a day. There have been some like totally asinine, bogus claims, bogus accusations about me, and I don't know this person, like I've been getting like messages asking me what's going on.
Looks like it posted there. Can you tell me know the name of it the name of the the control of video you said?
Victoria
Play the clip about beta. What's it called?
It's so many the name and I'll find it. I'm sorry. I'm a little bit out of it right now
Yeah
Everyone check out. Okay. This is ABBA on okay ABBA ABBA's last live about Crystal Anne that one
Okay
You're gonna see this one, okay
Okay, here you go
Mary's always got this phone call, she's a really busy lady.
He's talking about Chris, go on.
People block her and it's not because people don't like her,
it's just that she wrongs people and then she's the victim.
She's not the fucking victim.
She does this to herself and causes issues for other people.
And then she's like, oh, poor me,
it's because of that person, how dare they.
Verso Anne.
That's about talking about.
Everyone has to look up because she comes over and she creates all these weird problems.
And she brings you into it.
The same when she was talking to Rocky Ranger, she was like,
I want to take you to court, Leo Acton.
Blah, blah, blah.
You know?
It's too much.
People don't want to deal with people like that.
I had to listen to her every single day and I tried to calm her down.
She's gonna play the victim. That's what she's doing to everybody right now. She's playing the victim.
She's telling everybody, pull me out of use, me out of use. What the fuck? You sound like,
I told you I was like, you're not even making sense. Like, what the hell are you even saying?
I used you. How do I use you? What's that said for those two months that you didn't give me donos when I was on the phone to you, trying to help you out, trying to make your life a little bit better?
I was using you?
Girl, you send donos because apparently you're okay and well enough to look after your own funds and finances. Clearly you're not.
She does she asked me she asked me so many times to call up her judge
She's hot. She's to call up her DA and say that I'm a witness
She gets me involved in her court case and she's probably done it to Rocky Rainer as well
Where she's trying to involve him and a lot of people would just like I saw show you
I know I don't even believe you in the first place crystal. So I'm not doing it
And it's always about her the same when I saw her in Rick's chat
It's like Rick's talking and then she just goes on off on her own little freakin
tangent about me on her and I don't fucking know I still don't even get it all I know is it's not true
Do you have a police report? Wow you got a police report Crystal?
Maybe you can do a police report with me and say that I stole your money. Oh
Crystal maybe I haven't stolen anything sorry
Maybe you can tell them I freaking
Listen, five-boy breeze, we both know the truth when it comes to that beyond our stuff.
But I'm not gonna freaking go off and help her and call.
Go on, help her and call her what?
What's that call case about?
I promise she's taking gangles to call.
She's taking a bunch of people to call.
I'm probably gonna have to, she's gonna produce my name as well because, oh, she tells everybody,
well, I got a liar, I got a legal team.
Girl, they're probably thinking, what the fuck?
I'm probably thinking, what the fuck is she even talking about?
But we'll take our money, just because she called a legal team
doesn't mean that you go.
This is the case that was against Bianna that she lost.
And her dad had to pay $1,000 fine,
because Crystal had lied about everything.
His girlfriend, Chelsea, looked at the video before where
she pops in and talks about Crystal,
that she didn't even know her and never met her,
because she was trying to put a case on her, but she lost.
And I shared all of that and then Crystal left for a while.
I have all of that.
And also, Renee gave me permission to use her videos.
She didn't get rid of anything.
She's still around.
She covers crime and she's got a huge channel now, but she said she never got rid of the videos on crystal
She knows she's a nut and she was the one that busted her about the lies and the cord and
The Vienna was not her boyfriend. I and Chelsea had never met crystal
So she never came by her house and drove her foot like crystal was saying everything was lies and this is what?
What Abba's talking about and this was before she left and she did another nasty video to crystal that have that I
Shared it once I might share it again if she continues
But this is Abba talking about it because she the crystal try to drag us all into this fake
Lawson said legal team legal team. It was a bogus lawsuit against this guy because he was trying to move away
And she was stalking him at his job and trying to force a relationship and he had a girlfriend that beautiful girl Chelsea that you see in my other video. So, you know, check out the other videos and you'll see her very sweet innocent looks like a kid.
And she came forward because she was trying to find out what was going on with this woman online.
And she had never even been to Oklahoma. She lived outside of Oklahoma
She was being her girlfriend and now I believe they're married now
You've got a good case people take your money anyway
It is not true by any of these people. She said it about Bianca. She said that this poor kid, this poor innocent guy attacks her in the house.
When I have a witness on this freaking page right now, we were talking to her the exact same time that she said the incident happened.
We did it and he was on the phone to her.
Babe, it was on the phone with her.
It is sociopathic because this honestly the truth is when it comes to Bianca.
She fancied him, she had a crush on him, he lived with her, I don't think he basically fancied her back, she got pissed off, so then when he moved out, she was like, oh fuck him, fuck you, how dare you, then she said that she used him, and then she was like, oh he used me, stole my money, he ran over my toe, but then when that incident happened, then she said she took him to court because he came into her house.
Why didn't you go to the police at that point?
She didn't.
She didn't go to the police.
She waited two days off to us and then called the police up.
I hope she gets help as well. She needs to realize right now that she is not healthy.
Her mind is not, it was a revenge case. That's all it is. It was a fucking revenge case.
And I thought it was a drop-it.
I was like, maybe you can just move on. The honor is not saying anything. Just move on from it.
You know, she's like, no, the honor is a de-action.
So was that how it goes?
And then Chelsea or something?
She's like, no, definitely not a de-action.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Of course he is the master.
Of course he is, but she loves it.
She loves the attention.
Um, sure.
Uh, okay.
Well, that was interesting.
But, uh, yeah.
Well, you want to see the, um,
this is an interesting thing.
In 2012, they had an opening ceremony,
um,
for the Olympics.
This is in 2012.
Should just before, but it's pretty interesting.
and check it out you see it so that's preparing just like all the hospital
beds right okay
Thank you very much for watching!
Also by the NHL.
Electable islands neverland is the snuggest
You know
Distances between one adventure and the next. It's nicely
Found it by day with the table and chairs
It's not a bit frightening
But in the two minutes before you go to sleep
It is real
If you want to get rid of your beer belly in time for summer, check this out.
Hey, Dr.
Hey Paige, what's up?
Like the music?
Oh, yeah.
That was interesting.
I think they had, um, I think they had, um, it was a, I don't know, they did have a
lot of interesting music during that thing.
Yeah.
So let me see.
Anyone wants to come up?
That was that was pretty good, huh? Yeah, that was the opening ceremonies of the of the 2012 Olympics and
It looks kind of like it was like a
Kind of like a ritual and then so I don't know
Hey Nancy, how are you guys doing a little better? Yeah. Hi Lola. Hi Lola. Hi. This is Lola. How are you?
Yeah, I'm waiting for my yesterday. I dropped my phone
One's coming today
So I'll open up the panel if anyone wants to come up
Anyone's welcome
Well except, you know RG decided to pour and bomb me this morning
RG is unfortunately banned. I'm sorry if you were fans of RG
That he won't be able to show anymore
Because he's decided to to take up on this crazy
It's like it's like a little too much for me all this
all this
I mean, it's like these people are so obsessed with
The PDF stuff. It's it's gone gone too far
I don't want that in my like mind like all like all the talk of it. It's like it's really disturbing
And then of course, you know, since I got here everyone's been obsessed with it
I don't know if it's been like just part of the culture forever, but
Or just like I should have been by the coronavirus stuff or whatever. I don't know. It's like it just seems like it's I
Just call it cuckoo for cocoa puffs and it's like and then at the more you look into it
like all the people screaming the loudest about it have the most
Usually to hide I mean it's like so
You know, but that's one thing I did play this clip. This was I'll play it one more time. This was last night on
Alexandra's IRL news time she covered I guess they are responding to like a bunch of stuff, but
He did say something kind of interesting
And I'm just gonna play this one little clip of it
It was like three hours 19 or two hours 19 minutes, I think or two three hours 19 minutes
Okay, here you go
But yet you going around calling people pedophiles
You know if it wasn't so expensive if it wasn't a thought process that I can't get paid or I would lose money
I would sue the fuck out of you
You know and that's what really needs to happen. You know YouTube needs to get rid of a bunch of you people
Okay, you serve no purpose. You just get on here and you spread fake lies because your ass is hurt
Okay, Kate over there talking about groomers baby girls. You don't forget the thousands of dollars you put in my pocket
You're calling you. Oh, so she donated a whole bunch to him, too
Really groomer, but you forgot about the thousands of dollars that you put in my pocket
You hmm forget about the thousands of dollars that not only you put in my pocket
But you siphon to Barry and Barry put it in my pocket
Really?
Okay
Well, just block him. We can block him personally or if any has a problem with him you can block him
But um, I would recommend checking out the interview. There is a whole hour and a half interview that um
That Alexandra did with him and I and it's like there's more to the story than
Than what's being presented by a lot of people. Okay, and so I just recommend checking that
Checking that interview out. I will link that interview
I guess I'm gonna wrap up right now because I'm waiting for my phone to come but um
I'll get that link for you guys and you can check out for yourself and judge for yourself
I mean, but it's like I think it's not right that nobody can defend themselves against such serious allegations, you know
And so, I think it was on the IP2 wiki channel
a whole month ago.
And I'll link it for you guys.
Okay.
And really check this video out.
And then I'll play the join the cult video
and then we will catch up with you later.
But here's the link to
Let me see.
Maybe it was on the IRL news time.
OK, one second.
She's been doing great content lately regarding this.
Should be around here.
Let me see.
Live.
Well, I don't...
Where is it? Where? Is it the next day?
Oh, yeah, here it is. Okay.
It's on our channel. Here it is.
There you go. That's the link to that.
And, you know, Q, I guess Q's also banned from the show
because he porn-bought me the other day,
as well as who else porn-bought me.
I don't know, I think Arthur, I think Arthur probably,
not, I think J-Dog, I think we lost some people,
but you know what, this is like, it was so easy
for them to,
Turn on me, but here you go
Not a lot, but I think we have the right people here, okay, so yeah form bomb is really dumb here you go guys
Yeah, you can read energy but watch watch the interview and then read the energy there, okay, because there's a lot of like
projected energy, you know to
Right, and I think he's been the scapegoat and that's what they do to scapegoats is they project energy onto them
Right, yeah, I got the other retards like you. I'm Janney. Bye
Okay, here you go
Later guys
City could see me
Before I even spoke I don't know about that, but I'm still here
I've been walking in circles, baby, losing my direction
Same old face, it's selling perfect projections
Everybody swears that they got the truth
But I don't even know what I'm supposed to do
Then you show up on my feet like a premonition
Cards on the table, digital visions
You say, where are we? What's your avoiding?
Yeah, you got a way of making silence feel loud
They say you're dangerous, say it's all a game
But you're the only one calling me by name
No, yeah, no pressure, just to get in close to
come see me don't overthink it but i freeze every time i get close to the edge of it because the
world's got opinions on what this means and i don't even know what i'm feeling in yeah maybe it's
more than illusion something about you got me questioning conclusions every symbol every line
you draw feels like truth i've been running from and the voices in my head keep telling me
No pain, no pressure, just you're getting closer to your own sand
And the top they'll judge, but that's now
This is your turning I laugh it off but my chest starts burning
All this time I've been standing still While the world keeps asking me to feel
If I stay I'm safe but I'm fading If I go I might stop changing
Maybe that's the risk I need to finally be something real
Your heart evolved and every step forward means a song
And everything they told you to hold
You find yourself when you join the call